Do what I ordered you to do.
I don't want the risk
of that old woman recovering.
What happened to my mom?
I don't think I know you.
Doc Reyes. I'll go ahead.
Sorry, Ma'am.
Who are you?
Where am I?
Mommy, you're in the hospital.
Don't you really remember
anything?
Maybe you can show her things
that could bring
her memory back.
Does your head hurt?
If you remember what happened
to you, please tell me.
How's your mom?
Has she remembered anything?
Not yet.
And you, how are you?
Here, imitating you.
You never gave up.
I'm here to support you.
Thank you, Joey.
Amazing, you still have that.
I thought I lost it.
That's for you. One each for us.
Lucky you found it.
I don't think "luck"
is the word.
What then?
Fate.
[THUDS]
Because of your incompetence,
the problem got worse!
Rebecca should have been dead!
Berdugo, forgive me.
I'll make it up to you.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Give me one more chance, Boss.
Your stupidity cannot be
forgiven!
- [GUN FIRES]
- [SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
Get rid of him!
Or Berdugo will come after you
next.
[SINISTER MUSIC CONTINUES]
If Rebecca really has amnesia,
she should stay that way.
Her memory must not return.
Good morning, Ma'am.
Andrew just stepped out.
I'll call him back.
No!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Help me.
My life is in danger.
He will kill me...
I can't tell if the old woman
really remembers nothing.
The timing is too convenient.
She suddenly has amnesia now.
It could be real,
but she could also recover.
Will you wait
until she remembers?
If you want, I'll do it.
Not yet.
Rebecca is surely guarded now.
And besides, Andrew will never
leave her side.
He even hired security.
So, what's your plan now?
Ma'am, wait! You're hurting me.
- Ma'am...
- Help me, Clarissa.
My life is in danger,
and so are my children's lives.
Help me.
Help me, please.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Ma'am, what are you saying?
Can you remember everything?
Maybe you're just dreaming.
Wait, I'll call the doctor.
- No! No!
- I'll just call the doctor...
No one must know,
not even my children.
They'll be in greater danger.
I'm serious, Clarissa.
I'm serious.
Help me. I'm telling the truth,
Clarissa.
- I'm telling the truth!
- Ma'am, it hurts.
[REBECCA SCREAMING]
I am going to get the doctor!
Sorry! I didn't recognize her!
I thought she was someone else!
[GROANING]
Mom, calm down, calm down.
Mom, calm down.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [THUDDING]
- [GRUNTING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Ouch, it hurts!
Ouch! My arm got caught.
Sorry, Dad. I got carried away.
That was good.
But, child, what I'm teaching
you is only self-defense,
not for showing off, okay?
Yes, Dad.
But what's our next lesson?
What next lesson?
You've learned all my moves.
Then let's go to
the firing range.
How can I take you
to the firing range?
I can't even leave the house.
If we practice firing here,
the neighbors will complain.
Honestly,
I'm so bored here at home.
I don't even know
what's happening with the case
I'm putting up with.
Feels like I'll rot here.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
I'm really sorry.
I didn't think mommy would do
that to you.
It's okay, Ma'am.
That's how patients are
when agitated.
They become violent
and say random things.
Did mommy say something?
Like what?
I may have misheard again.
Before you came in,
Ma'am Rebecca seemed different.
What do you mean?
Can someone with amnesia
have a lucid moment?
Mom had a lucid moment?
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm not sure, Sir Tomas.
Maybe she was just dreaming
and woke up,
so she said random things.
That's okay.
Mommy could just be dreaming.
What did mommy say?
No one must know,
not even my children.
They'll be in greater danger.
I really couldn't understand,
Sir.
Sorry, Clarissa.
Take a break first. Go home.
We'll take care of mommy.
I'll call the driver
to take you home.
No need, Ma'am. I'm fine here.
Miss Clarissa, please.
Let the driver bring you home.
There's no problem.
Honestly,
we're the ones who owe you.
And Joey might get mad at me.
All right, thank you.
[STIRRING MUSIC]
[CLACKING]
Sorry, Sir! Sorry, sorry!
Fix it before Liza finds out.
Okay, Sir.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
We can't just let Jin Ho go.
He is dad's only lead
to the syndicate.
Why are we even talking
about this?
Didn't your dad say he
doesn't want you meddling
in his investigation?
I knew it,
you're planning something.
No way. Your dad will get mad.
But I want to do this for dad.
If we find the syndicate's
hideout as soon as possible,
they'll be caught faster.
And our suffering will end,
- especially dad's.
- Wait...
Ours?
Why am I included?
You'll be the one calling
Jin Ho.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
Is there a problem?
It bothered me that this woman's
face looked familiar.
And then I remembered something.
Look at this.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
You think this could be her?
The video is too blurry.
If she's that woman,
it means Jin Ho knows her.
That Korean is betraying you.
It's not impossible
he's betraying our group.
Go on.
You know, I can't be the one
to call him.
Last time we were together,
the police chased him.
He might suspect something.
I don't know, Joey.
I don't know.
He's our friend, but...
we're quick to think
badly of him.
He's still concerned about us.
He was with me when you
and Andrew left me at Valmora.
And he saved our lives
many times.
But dad has a lot of proof
against him.
And maybe he's just checking
on us because he's spying.
Hey, that's not true.
If that's what he was doing,
he would've told the syndicate
who you are.
[GUN COCKS]
Which do you prefer?
You take him out or I'll do it?
Put that away.
It might backfire on you.
If we kill him now,
we won't know his true
connection to that woman.
I want to know first
where this leads us.
Don't worry.
I'll handle this carefully.
And, Matias,
this stays between us.
Don't tell Berdugo yet.
After all, he's busy with his
family affairs.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
All right, here's the plan.
You call him,
then say we'll meet.
But what we'll really do
is follow him
- to see what he's doing...
- Okay, okay, I'll call him.
If we prove your suspicions
wrong,
would you tell your dad
to stop targeting Jin Ho?
Sure!
I'll even apologize to you
for suspecting your "oppa."
- All right! You said it, okay?
- Call him now.
I'm counting on your word
of honor.
Sure!
There.
- [PHONE RINGING]
- [FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Nothing, it just keeps ringing.
Text him.
Okay.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE CHIMES]
There, I tried.
I'll just try again later.
[PHONE CHIMES]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE RINGING]
- [SIGHS]
- [OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Why didn't you answer the phone?
Who was it?
Just a friend who wants
to meet up, but...
I know I can't go out.
That's why I ignored it.
Like I said, I'll do whatever
you want me to do.
If you want me to stay here,
I'll stay.
But you're sulking.
If you want to go see
your friend, go.
I'm worried about Clarissa.
If mommy sees her again,
she might hurt her.
Well, you're right.
I also don't understand
why mommy reacted that way
to Clarissa.
I was thinking not to let her
come here for now.
There are nurses anyway.
Wait, you're deciding too fast.
Didn't you think that if mommy's
memories are coming back,
then it's better
if Miss Clarissa is here?
What if mommy hurts Clarissa
again?
- That's embarrassing!
- But what if she doesn't?
What if Miss Clarissa
could help mommy remember?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I thought I'm a prisoner here?
Yes, but keeping you here
isn't doing me any good.
You always look bored,
you look upset.
And I know you.
You become more reckless
when you're unhappy.
So better if you just do
what you want to do.
Just remember to be careful.
I will.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE CHIMES]
Wait.
Hey, perfect, it's Jin Ho!
- Here.
- Let me see.
- There, he's just checking in.
- Invite him now.
Tell him we'll meet him.
Invite him right away?
Can't we just chat first?
Gosh! Even with Jin Ho,
you're shy.
You're exaggerating. I'm not.
Of course, I just don't want him
to think
I'm too eager to see him
right away.
You're being dramatic.
You'll just text him.
Tell him we'll meet,
and Andrew will be there too.
So...
The two of you are okay now?
Of course.
And Jin Ho is Andrew's
friend too.
And I think it's time
for a reunion.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Mom...
Are you okay?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Miss Clarissa mentioned you
had a lucid memory?
Are you okay now, Mom?
Can you remember anything?
Mom, please tell me.
Mom, please.
Mom, so we can find the one
who did this to you.
Please, Mom.
Is there?
- Andrew.
- Mom...
Don't pressure her.
You might get hurt.
Why are you interfering?
Don't you want mommy
to remember?
I you're not going to help,
then stay out of my business!
How dare you talk to me
like that?
[TENSE MUSIC]
Hon!
Don't argue with Andrew.
What's going on?
Stop this!
An you, why are you talking
to your brother like that?
He's just concerned with mommy
and the people around him!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Tomas.
I just couldn't stop myself.
I was thinking about
what Miss Clarissa told me.
I was hoping mom's memory
would return.
Is it really that important
for my memory to come back?
If I can still remember
something, then good.
But for now, be content
that we're together...
that I'm alive,
instead of fighting!
Andrew, please...
Okay, Mom. I'm sorry.
It won't happen again, Mom.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Love...
Make a small portion.
Your daughter said
she won't eat here.
She's going out with Peter.
Is that so?
Then let's just eat canned food.
No, finish cooking that.
It's already there.
All right, but wait...
Good to know you allowed
your daughter.
Of course. I'm the only one
under a house arrest,
not the whole family.
That's true.
What's with that?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Did she hurt you?
Ma'am Rebecca didn't do it
intentionally.
She suddenly lashed out earlier.
I don't even understand
what happened.
She suddenly asked me for help.
I don't know
if what she said was true.
You know she's not
in her right mind.
-Miguel...
-You shouldn't go there anymore.
She might do something to you.
Miguel, the person is sick.
Try to understand.
Even so!
I can't even go out because
I'm worried about you all.
Listen to me.
I don't want you to get hurt.
All right,
I'll talk to Ma'am Yvette.
Just relax.
Don't stress yourself...
Watch your heart.
Are we pushing through
or should we cancel?
No, we're pushing through.
It's just that, Andrew isn't
replying to my texts.
But I'll call him.
Does Andrew really need
to be there?
He might be busy with his mom.
Besides, he's not that close
to Jin Ho.
It's better if we're complete
when we meet Jin Ho.
[PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING]
And we need a better vehicle.
What if something happens?
Can your pick-up handle it?
- Now you're blaming my vehicle.
- The pick-up can't handle it.
I just got carried away earlier.
I know.
But Yvette is right.
You're stressed out.
Maybe you need a change
of environment,
even for a while.
That's why she asked me
to come here, to be with you.
Maybe I did overreact earlier.
But is it wrong to be emotional
when it comes to my mom?
Definitely not.
But it's not good
to put her under pressure.
She's already going through
a lot.
You're adding to her stress.
Andrew, if Aunt Rebecca
needs time to recover,
you also need a break.
Tell me, when was the last time
you did something
other than watch over your mom?
It's been a while.
Even the Tirada ,
I've been neglecting it too.
Wait, no, no, no.
We're not going to talk
about work.
I know.
Let's go watch a movie,
so you can get your mind
off things. Is that okay?
Let's do that?
[PHONE RINGING]
Sorry, excuse me.
Hello?
Andrew, good thing you answered.
Sorry...
I wasn't checking my messages.
Wait, is there a problem?
Peter and I plan to confront
Jin Ho.
Are you joining?
Yes, sure.
Text me where you are.
All right.
Let's go to the meeting place
ahead of him.
Then we'll plan how
to corner Jin Ho.
Okay, I'm on my way.
Okay, bye. Take care.
Wait.
You're leaving?
Zoey, I'm sorry.
Something really important
came up.
I'll make it up to you.
Wait, so you're just leaving me
here?
Sorry.
Andrew!
[BRAZEN MUSIC PLAYING]
Jackpot! That's our target.
[CAR REVVING]
Come on, let's follow him.
- [REVVING]
- [BRAZEN MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WHIRRING]
You're going somewhere?
Yeah, I'm meeting
with my friend.
You're okay with that, right?
Yes, just be careful.
- [WHIRRING]
- [OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGS]
Joey?
Hello, Andrew?
Are you there already?
I'm here.
I'm just looking for a spot
where we can talk.
We're almost there too.
But there's a problem.
Peter's tire burst.
Because you don't even check it.
Wow! You have the nerve to blame
and you're not even helping.
I'm sorry, okay?
Do you need help?
I can go there.
No, it's fine.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
And it's almost done anyway.
We're going there.
Because after 20 million years,
Peter finally fixed his tire.
- It's fine now, right?
- It's almost done.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Joey, wait, okay?
Hello, Joey?
Andrew, what's that?
Sorry, Joey,
I thought there was...
Andrew, what's happening?
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Andrew!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I have no idea who did this
to my brother.
We both know Andrew has done
a lot of exposés,
so lots of people are angry
with him.
We're just here to visit
Andrew Dizon.
Sorry. Ma'am Zoey gave strict
orders.
No one can enter.
Hey, Zoey, come out!
Face us!
Zoey!
You know? I have an idea
who did this.
Only one person knew
we were going there.
Seems impossible.
If not him, then who?
That should serve as a lesson
to your brother.
He should be careful
who he crosses.